hello think about a forward gain
transfer function represented as 2 l/ s
+ 2 * s + 3 integrated to a system
featuring a Unity gain feedback
path the transer function for the closed
loop system can be written as GS over 1
plus GS and can be further simplified as
follows when we use a step input as our
reference signal the output YT will have
the shape of this form to achieve better
control of the output we can introduce a
controller to the system let's consider
adding a controller for our system
represented as s+ 2/ s+
10 now the close loop transfer function
for our system is gscs over 1 plus
gscs and can be further simplified as
follows